eventbu.com 2018-10-08

# Privacy Policy

"Provider" service portal Eventbu.com

"User" is a visitor service portal Eventbu.com

"Event" is a page on the portal Eventbu.com, which informs about the fact what is happening

Type of data that we collect.

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored on your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your device so we can deliver a desirable experience. Our systems also automatically log information like your browser, operating system.

We also may collect personal information such as IP address (traffic and debugging). We also may collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us: Facebook ID and Facebook Access Token (events read only).

We also may collect provided information such as name, email, phone number etc. associated with specific event or event organizator.

We take those facts, mentioned above, as our legitimate interest, in order to deliver save and better experience.

Data storage time.

For anonymous data we may keep data indefinitely. In other case we keep data for 3 months at maximum time period.

We don't share your personal data with other companies.

We generally do not share or sell information to other companies.

You can request to see your data.

You can request access to your personal data being stored by provider. You can also ask us to correct, update or delete any Personal Data that we process about them. Data protection law provides you with rights in respect of personal data that we hold about you, including the right to request a copy of the personal data, request that we rectify, restrict or delete your personal data, object to profiling and unsubscribe from marketing communications. Provider is a data administrator.

You can ask privacy questions.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:

allevents.com@gmail.com

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. 

We take steps to protect personal information

We take reasonable steps to secure anonymous and personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt communication with SSL certificate. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.
